Guide to the Howard Brubaker Papers MSS.053
Fales Library and Special Collections
The Howard Brubaker Papers
1907-1957
Fales Library and Special Collections
Brubaker, Howard, 1882-1957
MSS.053
18 Linear Feet (12 boxes)
Howard Brubaker was an editor (Success and Liberator) and a contributor to many other periodicals from 1918 through the 1950's, including: Collier's, The New Yorker, The New Republic, and Saturday Evening Post. Many of his contributions were political in nature and reflected his, at times, left-of-center point of view. The collection includes his manuscripts and copies of journals to which he contributed. Brubaker died in 1957.
18 linear feet (12 boxes)
Provenance
The Howard Brubaker Papers are comprised of two distinct collections of Brubaker material, one of which was donated directly to the Fales Library and the other, which was transfered to the Fales Library from the Franklin D. Roosevelt Library in 1993. This collection was donated to the Franklin D. Roosevelt library by Mrs. Howard Brubaker on August 14, 1974. The two collections have been interfiled.
Access Restrictions
Materials are open to researchers. Please contact the Fales Library and Special Collections, fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
Historical/Biographical Note:
Howard Brubaker was an editor of Success and Liberator and a contributor to Collier's Weekly, The New Republic, Saturday Evening Post, Country Gentleman, and many other magazines. He published over 100 short stories and a number of non-fiction pieces on contemporary affairs, especially national politics. He is best known for "Of All Things", a by-liner column that ran weekly in the New Yorker for over twenty-five years. This column was composed of six or eight two sentence paragraphs that offered humorous and satirical comments on contemporary happenings and personages. Many of these brief paragraphs were reprinted in newspapers across the country.
Scope and Content Note
The Howard Brubaker Papers are a part of the Fales Library, New York University. The Fales Library is the primary special collections division of the NYU libraries, housing nearly 200,000 volumes of English and American literature from 1700 to the present. Strengths of the collection include the development of the English and American novel, with an emphasis on the Gothic and the Victorian novel.
The papers consist of typescript copies of short stories, press clippings, and correspondence from family, various leftist and liberal organizations, literary agents, editors, publishers and fans.
SERIES DESCRIPTION
Series I consists of Brubaker's original short story and newspaper column manuscripts, rough drafts, and story and column ideas and worksheets.
Series II consists of magazines, newspapers, and periodicals in which Brubaker's stories, paragraphs, and bon mots appeared in print.
Series III consists of Brubaker's personal and literary correspondence.
Series IV consists of Brubaker's financial and tax statements.
Series V consists of unprocessed newspaper clippings, mostly clipped by the Roemike clipping service, of Brubaker's appearances in newspapers across the country.
Series VI consists of a single box of oversized materials.
Arrangement
Folders are generally arranged alphabetically by subject.
The files are grouped into six series.
Related Material at the Fales Library and Special Collections
The Geoffrey T. Hellman Papers; Hellman was another frequent contributor to the New Yorker during the same period.
Magazines (Periodicals); Magazines (Periodicals); Journalists |v Correspondence.; Journalists |v Correspondence.; Journalists |v Biography.; Journalists |v Biography.; Political satire, American.; Political satire, American.; Press and politics.; Press and politics.; Food |v Periodicals.; Food |v Periodicals.; New York (N.Y.) -- Intellectual life -- 20th century.; New York (N.Y.) -- Intellectual life -- 20th century.; Cookery |v Periodicals.; Cookery |v Periodicals.; Food writing.; Food writing.; United States |x Politics and government |y 1919-1933.; United States |x Politics and government |y 1919-1933.; United States |x Politics and government |y 1923-1929.; United States |x Politics and government |y 1923-1929.; Neutrality.; Neutrality.; Cookery, American.; Cookery, American.; United States |x Politics and government |y 1900-1945 |v Periodicals.; United States |x Politics and government |y 1900-1945 |v Periodicals.; Socialists -- United States.; Socialists -- United States.; Liberator (New York, N.Y.: 1918); New republic (New York, N.Y.).; New republic (New York, N.Y.).; Manuscripts for publication.; Manuscripts for publication.; New York (N.Y.).; Collier's weekly.; Clippings (information artifacts); Country gentleman (Albany, N.Y.: 1898); Correspondence.; New York (N.Y.).; Photographs.; Clippings (information artifacts); Diaries; New Yorker (New York, N.Y.: 1925); PM (New York, N.Y.: Daily); Correspondence.; Photographs.; Diaries; Perkins, Frances, 1880-1965; Benton, William, 1900-1973; Perkins, Frances, 1880-1965; Bliven, Bruce, 1889-1977; Benton, William, 1900-1973; Brubaker, Howard, 1882-1957; Bliven, Bruce, 1889-1977; Brubaker, Howard, 1882-1957; Ross, Harold Wallace, 1892-1951; Ross, Harold Wallace, 1892-1951; McMahon, Brien, 1903-1952; McMahon, Brien, 1903-1952
- Series I: Original manuscripts and drafts
  - "Appointments and Disappointments", undated (Box I:1, Folder 1)
  - "April! April!", undated (Box I:1, Folder 2)
  - "Aunt Mary, Preferred", undated (Box I:1, Folder 3)
  - "A Bachelor Saga", undated (Box I:1, Folder 4)
  - "A Bad Actor", undated (Box I:1, Folder 5)
  - "The Ballyhoover", undated (Box I:1, Folder 6)
  - "Barbarous Barbara", undated (Box I:1, Folder 7)
  - "The Battle of Frogtown Harbor", undated (Box I:1, Folder 8)
  - "The Battle of 1928" (Box I:1, Folder 9)
  - "A Bird of Passage", undated (Box I:1, Folder 10)
  - "Boy-About-Town", undated (Box I:1, Folder 11)
  - "Boy Finance", undated (Box I:1, Folder 12)
  - "The Boy of Destiny", undated (Box I:1, Folder 13)
  - "Boy Power", undated (Box I:1, Folder 14)
  - "The Boy Spout", undated (Box I:1, Folder 15)
  - "Bud Marries a Drab", undated (Box I:1, Folder 16)
  - "Cabbages and Queens", undated (Box I:1, Folder 17)
  - "The Chaimberlain Method", undated (Box I:1, Folder 18)
  - "Class Conscious Karen", undated (Box I:1, Folder 19)
  - "Clay Feet", undated (Box I:1, Folder 20)
  - "The Comic Stripling", undated (Box I:1, Folder 21)
  - "Con Game", undated (Box I:1, Folder 22)
  - "The Conquering Connie Comes", undated (Box I:1, Folder 23)
  - "Constant Reader", undated (Box I:1, Folder 24)
  - "The Country Preacher" (miscellaneous drafts), undated (Box I:1, Folder 25)
  - "The Country Preacher (The Run-Aways)", undated (Box I:1, Folder 26)
  - "The Cruise of the Cleopatra", undated (Box I:1, Folder 27)
  - "The Cruise of the Fearless Four", undated (Box I:1, Folder 28)
  - "Daguerreos of Memory (Experiments in Falsehood)" (Charles Herbert Bass), undated (Box I:1, Folder 29)
  - "Daredevil Dayton", undated (Box I:1, Folder 30)
  - "Daughter Knows Best", undated (Box I:1, Folder 31)
  - "Dawn Family - 100,000 B.C. (Little Kim - Cave Child Prodigy)", undated (Box I:1, Folder 32)
  - "Dear Dead Days", undated (Box I:1, Folder 33)
  - "Decline and Fall", undated (Box I:1, Folder 34)
  - "The Double Doublecross", undated (Box I:1, Folder 35)
  - "The Dream of a Constant Reader", undated (Box I:1, Folder 36)
  - "Enemy Wanted", undated (Box I:1, Folder 37)
  - "The Evils of Intemperance", undated (Box I:1, Folder 38)
  - "Fairy Way and Other Child's Verses by Charles Herbert Bass", undated (Box I:1, Folder 39)
  - "Fast and Loose", undated (Box I:1, Folder 40)
  - "Flickering Shadows", undated (Box I:1, Folder 41)
  - "A Fugitive From Injustice", undated (Box I:1, Folder 42)
  - "Gas", undated (Box I:1, Folder 43)
  - "The G-Boy", undated (Box I:1, Folder 44)
  - "Generally Speaking: A Thirty-Minute Program by Lee A. Cavalier", undated (Box I:1, Folder 45)
  - "Gold Is Where You Find It", undated (Box I:1, Folder 46)
  - "The Gold-Digger Twins", undated (Box I:1, Folder 47)
  - "The Golden Haze", undated (Box I:1, Folder 48)
  - "Goodbye To All That", undated (Box I:1, Folder 49)
  - "A Grandpa Story for David on his Sixth Birthday", undated (Box I:1, Folder 50)
  - "Greeks Bearing Gifts", undated (Box I:1, Folder 51)
  - "Guest Artist", undated (Box I:1, Folder 52)
  - "Hand Made", undated (Box I:1, Folder 53)
  - "A Hank Town Comedy", undated (Box I:1, Folder 54)
  - "He Knew His Onions", undated (Box I:1, Folder 55)
  - "Helpful Herman", undated (Box I:1, Folder 56)
  - "His Good Name", undated (Box I:1, Folder 57)
  - "The Holy War", undated (Box I:1, Folder 58)
  - "Hope's Diamond", undated (Box I:1, Folder 59)
  - "Horizontal Prophets", undated (Box I:1, Folder 60)
  - "Hot Numbers", undated (Box I:1, Folder 61)
  - "The House of Livingstone", undated (Box I:1, Folder 62)
  - "How It All Began", undated (Box I:1, Folder 63)
  - "Including Lola", undated (Box I:1, Folder 64)
  - "Indirect Action", undated (Box I:1, Folder 65)
  - "Jerry-Go-Round", undated (Box I:1, Folder 66)
  - "A Journey into Journalism", undated (Box I:1, Folder 67)
  - "Junior Partners", undated (Box I:1, Folder 68)
  - "Just a Big, Happy Family", undated (Box I:1, Folder 69)
  - "Laughing With the News", undated (Box I:1, Folder 70)
  - "Lead Pencil Profits", undated (Box I:1, Folder 71)
  - "Life is Just a Bowl of Raspberries", undated (Box I:1, Folder 72)
  - "The Lion Tamers", undated (Box I:1, Folder 73)
  - "Listen, Lester!", undated (Box I:1, Folder 74)
  - "Little Big Sisters", undated (Box I:1, Folder 75)
  - "Little Bright Eyes", undated (Box I:1, Folder 76)
  - "Little Friends of All the Arts", undated (Box I:1, Folder 77)
  - "Little Junior Monologues and Other Rhymed Child-Whimseys" (Charles Herbert Bass), undated (Box I:1, Folder 78)
  - "Local Girl Makes Good", undated (Box I:1, Folder 79)
  - "The Malady Lingers On", undated (Box I:1, Folder 80)
  - "The Man Next Door", undated (Box I:1, Folder 81)
  - "The Man Who Hated Baseball", undated (Box I:1, Folder 82)
  - "The Man Without a Country Club", undated (Box I:1, Folder 83)
  - "Maizie Ought to Know", undated (Box I:1, Folder 84)
  - "A Midsummer Nightmare", undated (Box I:1, Folder 85)
  - "The Milk Pitcher", undated (Box I:1, Folder 86)
  - "Mixed Doubles", undated (Box I:1, Folder 87)
  - "Much Ado About Nutty", undated (Box I:1, Folder 88)
  - "Neighbor Trouble", undated (Box I:1, Folder 89)
  - "A Needle in a Haystack", undated (Box I:1, Folder 90)
  - "Neighbor Union", undated (Box I:1, Folder 91)
  - "New Occasions", undated (Box I:1, Folder 92)
  - "The Official Lyre", undated (Box I:1, Folder 93)
  - "One Pinned on Jim Smiley", undated (Box I:1, Folder 94)
  - "Opened by Mistake", undated (Box I:1, Folder 95)
  - "Operation Sister", undated (Box I:1, Folder 96)
  - "Over the Bounding Main", undated (Box I:1, Folder 97)
  - "The Parable of the Asters", undated (Box I:1, Folder 98)
  - "Party Lines", undated (Box I:1, Folder 99)
  - "Pen in Hand", undated (Box I:1, Folder 100)
  - "Poems" (Charles Herbert Bass), undated (Box I:1, Folder 101)
  - "Politcal Stories According to 'Elmer'" by Felix Ray (pseud.), undated (Box I:2, Folder 1)
  - "The Power of the Press", undated (Box I:2, Folder 2)
  - "A Problem Man", undated (Box I:2, Folder 3)
  - "The Professor Looks at Barbara", undated (Box I:2, Folder 4)
  - "Progress Toward Peace", undated (Box I:2, Folder 5)
  - "Rainbows", undated (Box I:2, Folder 6)
  - "Ranny and the Higher Life", undated (Box I:2, Folder 7)
  - "Rough Company", undated (Box I:2, Folder 8)
  - "A Round Trip to Crime", undated (Box I:2, Folder 9)
  - "Ruby Common", undated (Box I:2, Folder 10)
  - "Ruby Crosses the Rubicon", undated (Box I:2, Folder 11)
  - "A Rugged Individual", undated (Box I:2, Folder 12)
  - "Salvage", undated (Box I:2, Folder 13)
  - "Second Fiddle", undated (Box I:2, Folder 14)
  - "A Short Wife and a Gay One", undated (Box I:2, Folder 15)
  - "Silent Sally", undated (Box I:2, Folder 16)
  - "Silver Lining", undated (Box I:2, Folder 17)
  - "Soiled Wings", undated (Box I:2, Folder 18)
  - "Sparta", undated (Box I:2, Folder 19)
  - "The Spirit of Thirty-Six", undated (Box I:2, Folder 20)
  - "Spring Practice", undated (Box I:2, Folder 21)
  - "Springtime for Herbert", undated (Box I:2, Folder 22)
  - "Stardust", undated (Box I:2, Folder 23)
  - "Stick-in-the-Mud", undated (Box I:2, Folder 24)
  - "Surprise in the "Ead'nin'", undated (Box I:2, Folder 25)
  - "Sweet Spirits of Arcadia" (tentative title), undated (Box I:2, Folder 26)
  - "Take It To Tink", undated (Box I:2, Folder 27)
  - "A Tame Hero", undated (Box I:2, Folder 28)
  - "A Tangled Web", undated (Box I:2, Folder 29)
  - "A Tank Town Drama", undated (Box I:2, Folder 30)
  - "Think Tank Town", undated (Box I:2, Folder 31)
  - "Thoughts on Pedestrians", undated (Box I:2, Folder 32)
  - "Three Hardboiled Eggs", undated (Box I:2, Folder 33)
  - "Tight Rope", undated (Box I:2, Folder 34)
  - "Tinkering With Tink", undated (Box I:2, Folder 35)
  - "To the Aid of the Party", undated (Box I:2, Folder 36)
  - "Trying It On the Dog", undated (Box I:2, Folder 37)
  - "Two Birds", undated (Box I:2, Folder 38)
  - "Uncivil Government", undated (Box I:2, Folder 39)
  - "Unfinished Business", undated (Box I:2, Folder 40)
  - "Unfinished Jew Story (The Jews Are Like That)", undated (Box I:2, Folder 41)
  - "The Unmarried Miss Brazelton", undated (Box I:2, Folder 42)
  - "Unprepared As I Am Tonight...", undated (Box I:2, Folder 43)
  - "Votes For Babies", undated (Box I:2, Folder 44)
  - "The Wagon and the Star", undated (Box I:2, Folder 45)
  - "The Way of the Reformer", undated (Box I:2, Folder 46)
  - "The World Conqueror", undated (Box I:2, Folder 47)
  - "The Writing on the Wallpaper", undated (Box I:2, Folder 48)
  - "Young-Man-Afraid-of-His-Future", undated (Box I:2, Folder 49)
  - "Young Man River", undated (Box I:2, Folder 50)
  - "Youth Ache", undated (Box I:2, Folder 51)
  - Miscellaneous Drafts - Prose (Charles Herbert Bass), undated (Box I:2, Folder 52)
  - Miscellaneous Drafts, undated (Box I:2, Folder 53)
  - Miscellaneous Drafts, undated (Box I:2, Folder 54)
  - Typescripts, Originals and Notes for Brubaker's columns, undated (Box I:2, Folder 55)
  - Typescripts, Originals and Notes for Brukeker's columns, undated (Box I:2, Folder 56)
  - Photocopies of Newspaper Clippings of "Brubaker Says!", undated (Box I:2, Folder 57)
  - Photocopies of Miscellaneous Clippings, undated (Box I:2, Folder 58)
  - Miscellaneous Story Ideas, undated (Box I:2, Folder 59)
  - Miscellaneous Photos and Cartoons, undated (Box I:2, Folder 60)
- Series II: Magazines, Newspapers and Miscellaneous Periodicals
  - American Cookery / Boston Cooking School Magazine (incomplete run from 1900-1932) (Box II:1, Folder data_value_missing_a4ec64d13bcf08738e705e285df1a2f2)
  - Year Book for the Dutch Treat Club, MCMXXIII (1923) (Box II:1, Folder data_value_missing_5d9e97ce2be27fc08d4894891856cfe7)
  - The Players (membership book), 1914 (Box II:1, Folder data_value_missing_2b4eda46459331b90818e64ae695f49f)
  - Liberator, August, 1918 (Box II:2, Folder 1)
  - Liberator, October, 1918 (Box II:2, Folder 2)
  - Liberator, January, 1919 (Box II:2, Folder 3)
  - Liberator, February, 1919 (Box II:2, Folder 4)
  - Liberator, May, 1919 (Box II:2, Folder 5)
  - Liberator, August, 1919 (Box II:2, Folder 6)
  - Liberator, September, 1919 (Box II:2, Folder 7)
  - Liberator, December, 1919 (Box II:2, Folder 8)
  - Liberator, February, 1920 (Box II:2, Folder 9)
  - Liberator, March, 1920 (Box II:2, Folder 10)
  - Liberator, April, 1920 (Box II:2, Folder 11)
  - Liberator, July, 1920 (Box II:2, Folder 12)
  - Liberator, September, 1920 (Box II:2, Folder 13)
  - Liberator, October, 1920 (Box II:2, Folder 14)
  - Liberator, November, 1920 (Box II:2, Folder 15)
  - Liberator, December, 1920 (Box II:2, Folder 16)
  - Liberator, January, 1921 (Box II:2, Folder 17)
  - Liberator, February, 1921 (Box II:2, Folder 18)
  - Liberator, March, 1921 (Box II:2, Folder 19)
  - Liberator, April, 1921 (Box II:2, Folder 20)
  - Liberator, May, 1921 (Box II:2, Folder 21)
  - Liberator, June, 1921 (Box II:2, Folder 22)
  - Liberator, July, 1921 (Box II:2, Folder 23)
  - Liberator, August, 1921 (Box II:2, Folder 24)
  - Liberator, September, 1921 (Box II:2, Folder 25)
  - Liberator, October, 1921 (Box II:2, Folder 26)
  - Liberator, November, 1921 (Box II:2, Folder 27)
  - Liberator, December, 1921 (Box II:2, Folder 28)
  - Liberator, January, 1922 (Box II:2, Folder 29)
  - Liberator, February, 1922 (Box II:2, Folder 30)
  - Liberator, March, 1922 (Box II:2, Folder 31)
  - Liberator, April, 1922 (Box II:2, Folder 32)
  - Liberator, May, 1922 (Box II:2, Folder 33)
  - Liberator, June, 1922 (Box II:2, Folder 34)
  - Liberator, July, 1922 (Box II:2, Folder 35)
  - Liberator, August, 1922 (Box II:2, Folder 36)
  - Liberator, September, 1922 (Box II:2, Folder 37)
  - Clipping from The New-England Weekly Journal; Apr. 8, 1728, undated (Box II:2, Folder 38)
  - The Tiger (Warsaw IN, Warsaw High School, Yearbook), 1917 (Box II:2, Folder 39)
  - War - What For, 1932 (Box II:2, Folder 40)
  - Good Morning; Jan. 1, Jan. 15, Feb. 1, Mar. 1-15, Apr. 1, May 1-15, Jun. 15 - Jul. 1, undated (Box II:2, Folder 41)
  - Everybody's; Mar., 1926, Aug. 1926 (Box II:2, Folder 42)
  - The Masses, March, 1917 (Box II:2, Folder 43)
  - Correct Eating, January, 1925 (Box II:2, Folder 44)
  - Nature Magazine, January, 1925 (Box II:2, Folder 45)
  - College Humor; Nov. 1936, Dec. 1936, Jul. 1937, Aug. 1937, Dec. 1937, 1936-1937 (Box II:2, Folder 46)
  - Life, July, 1934 (Box II:2, Folder 47)
  - Life, October, 1934 (Box II:2, Folder 48)
  - Life, November, 1934 (Box II:2, Folder 49)
  - Life, December, 1934 (Box II:2, Folder 50)
  - Life, January, 1935 (Box II:2, Folder 51)
  - Life, February, 1935 (Box II:2, Folder 52)
  - Life, April, 1935 (Box II:2, Folder 53)
  - Life, May, 1935 (Box II:2, Folder 54)
  - Life, June, 1935 (Box II:2, Folder 55)
  - Life, July, 1935 (Box II:2, Folder 56)
  - Life, August, 1935 (Box II:2, Folder 57)
  - Life, October, 1935 (Box II:2, Folder 58)
  - Life, January, 1936 (Box II:2, Folder 59)
  - Life, May, 1936 (Box II:2, Folder 60)
  - Life; Aug. 1936, Sept. 1936 (Box II:2, Folder 61)
  - Life, October, 1936 (Box II:2, Folder 62)
  - Life, November, 1936 (Box II:2, Folder 63)
  - Redbook, January, 1925 (Box II:2, Folder 64)
  - Redbook, February, 1925 (Box II:2, Folder 65)
  - Redbook, March, 1925 (Box II:2, Folder 66)
  - Gourmet, March, 1941 (Box II:2, Folder 67)
  - Gourmet, December, 1941 (Box II:2, Folder 68)
  - Gourmet, April, 1942 (Box II:2, Folder 69)
  - Gourmet, July, 1942 (Box II:2, Folder 70)
  - Gourmet, August, 1942 (Box II:2, Folder 71)
  - Gourmet, October, 1942 (Box II:2, Folder 72)
  - Gourmet, May, 1949 (Box II:2, Folder 73)
  - Good Housekeeping, March, 1921 (Box II:2, Folder 74)
  - W omen's City Club of New York Quarterly, June, 1930 (Box II:2, Folder 75)
  - Women's City Club of New York Quarterly, October, 1930 (Box II:2, Folder 76)
  - Liberty, December 21, 1940 (Box II:2, Folder 77)
  - The Gregg Writer; Sept. 1940, Oct. 1940, Nov. 1940, Dec. 1940 (Box II:2, Folder 78)
  - The New Yorker, February 16, 1957 (Box II:2, Folder 79)
  - The Epicure, Spring & Summer 1949 (Box II:2, Folder 80)
  - Harper's Monthly Magazine: February, 1914 March, 1914 April, 1914 July, 1914 September, 1914 October, 1914 November, 1914 December, 1914 July, 1915 August, 1915 September, 1915 October, 1915 November, 1915 July, 1916 August, 1916 September, 1916 November, 1916 January, 1918 March, 1919 July, 1920 April, 1921 May, 1921, 1914-1921 (Box 3, Folder data_value_missing_e539cda2473c92a52a77960e9f5ff8a5)
  - The American Magazine: March, 1931 February, 1932 August, 1932 March, 1933 April, 1934 June, 1934 November, 1934 February, 1935 May, 1935 November, 1935 May, 1936 May, 1937 September, 1937 May, 1938, 1931-1938 (Box 3, Folder data_value_missing_9d9d669ca6a0260707f8490220f4e676)
  - Country Gentleman: December 22, 1917 July 18, 1925 August 15, 1925 September, 1925 December, 1925 May, 1926 July, 1926 October, 1926 January, 1927 April, 1927 March, 1928 February, 1929 June, 1929 October, 1929 March, 1930 August, 1930 April, 1931 August, 1932 March, 1934 September, 1934 October, 1935, 1917-1935 (Box 4, Folder data_value_missing_5046b0f0b046fe843020565610b5364c)
  - PM: June 14, 1940 June 18, 1940 June 19, 1940 June 20, 1940 June 23, 1940 June 24, 1940 June 25, 1940 June 26, 1940 June 27, 1940 June 28, 1940 June 30, 1940 July 1, 1940 July 2, 1940 July 3, 1940 July 4, 1940 July 5, 1940 July 7, 1940 July 8, 1940 July 9, 1940 July 10, 1940 July 11, 1940 July 12, 1940 July 14, 1940 July 15, 1940 July 16, 1940 July 17, 1940 July 18, 1940 July 19, 1940 July 21, 1940 July 22, 1940 July 23, 1940 July 24, 1940 July 31, 1940 August 16, 1940 September 11, 1940 (Box 4, Folder data_value_missing_51bb39cbf8ac571bbee0246432e1db74)
  - The Saturday Evening Post: August 20, 1921 February 2, 1924, 1921-1924 (Box 4, Folder data_value_missing_bf6e53f7f8d1e15c766e6e9eb688c898)
  - Life: August 29, 1938 (Box 4, Folder data_value_missing_9e77ede374026aff5aae293b75110a36)
  - Stage: April, 1937 November, 1937 (Box 4, Folder data_value_missing_601d97b18f00ed64ec7d5c32d02e4ca6)
  - Woman's Home Companion: April, 1925 (Box 4, Folder data_value_missing_9cf69a089c05b36fdb0e63b7f4b3540f)
  - The American Home: September, 1960 (Box 4, Folder data_value_missing_a3c840347086c594cf02820013c0639e)
  - Collier's: March 30, 1918 June 28, 1919 October 16, 1920 March 26, 1921 May 21, 1921 June 7, 1930, 1918-1930 (Box 4, Folder data_value_missing_40662d7bcdf277fd4a57a0c28aec3533)
  - Delineator: September, 1930 (Box 4, Folder data_value_missing_ef2aa8c1b9ca9749eede647a21a4b3cb)
  - This Week Magazine (New York Herald-Tribune): February 28, 1943 (Box 4, Folder data_value_missing_2ddcd61ac981354db5308a82803059b2)
  - Maclean's: April 15, 1942 (Box 4, Folder data_value_missing_bef0181a37389553c9b87440a79696e5)
  - The Freeman: April 13, 1921 (Box 4, Folder data_value_missing_8cacfa7422eb4cab81868dd9c3edb48c)
  - Success: June, 1907 July, 1907 August, 1907 September, 1907 November, 1907 December, 1907 January, 1908 February, 1908 March, 1908 June, 1908 July, 1908 October, 1908 December, 1908 January, 1909 February, 1909 March, 1909 April, 1909 May, 1909 June, 1909 August, 1909 September, 1909 October, 1909 November, 1909 April, 1911 May, 1911 June, 1911 July, 1911 August, 1911 October, 1911 December, 1911 October, 1921 November, 1921 December, 1921 January, 1922 February, 1922 March, 1922 April, 1922 May, 1922 June, 1922 July, 1922 August, 1922 September, 1922, 1907-1922 (Box 5, Folder data_value_missing_480a3d09ede50f80b97415eb68072800)
  - The Unemployed: December, 1930 Spring, 1931, 1930-1931 (Box 5, Folder data_value_missing_aa6e29266ad76bfb70fe009192886404)
  - The American Magazine: December, 1927 January, 1928 May, 1928 June, 1928 July, 1928 April, 1929 August, 1929 May, 1930 October, 1940, 1927-1940 (Box 5, Folder data_value_missing_5c320b326db7acefff5bfbf20d3ec044)
  - Scribner's, May, 1915 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Scribner's, May, 1915 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Scribner's, May, 1921 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Scribner's, October, 1929 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Scribner's, October, 1929 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Century, December, 1907 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Century, June, 1922 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Masonic News; March, 1928; April, 1928 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Monthly News Published by the New York League of Women Voters, March, 1939 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - The Handle of Connecticut; June 2, June 16, June 30, July 7, undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - The Crystal, June, 1925 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Congressional Record, January 3, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 12)